gatheringmagic.com 2019-06-01

# Disclosure & Privacy Policy | Article by GatheringMagic.com

Main » Articles » Disclosure & Privacy Policy

This page will outline both our Disclosure Policy as well as our Privacy Policy. Though they are rather annoying lawyer speak, they are not overly difficult to process and understand. If there are questions about either policy, please contact us! 

## Disclosure Policy

This blog is a sponsored blog created or supported by a company, organization or group of organizations. For questions about this blog, please contact Evan Erwin (evan@coolstuffinc.com). 

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, or other forms of compensation. 

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content. 

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites, and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers' own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. 

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified. 

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you respond to a survey, fill out a form, or leave a comment. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To improve our website 

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow), and this enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture or remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/). 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on March 2nd, 2012. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

CoolStuffInc.com 

8550 S. US Hwy 17-92 

Maitland, FL 32751 

USA 

evan@coolstuffinc.com 

TAGS
